A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1978
  - United States, 1978; 1978/200
    - Worldwatch Institute, Brown, Lester (Supplementary Material), 1978 (Reel 40, Frame 450)
    - Wo-Wu, 1978 (Reel 40, Frame 865)
    - Yale University (Master's Program in Afro-American Studies), 1978 (Reel 40, Frame 1077)
    - Yale University (B-W), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - Young Filmmakers/Video Arts, 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 150)
    - Young Filmmakers/Video Arts (Supplementary Material), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 165)
    - Y-Z, 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 345)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/200.A
      - American Institute of Stress, 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 515)
      - Baylor College of Medicine, 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 566)
      - Boston University (M), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 571)
      - Columbia University, Medical School (Goodman, DeWitt S.), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 594)
      - Massachusetts General Hospital (H-O), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 605)
      - D-Y, 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 719)
    - United States - Nursing, 1978; 1978/200.C
      - University of Wisconsin, Oshkosh (Nursing School), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 895)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1978; 1978/200.R
      - Sarah Lawrence College (Women's Studies), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 899)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1978; 1978/200.W
      - Clark Foundation (Cook, Joseph A.), 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 1040)
  - Philippines, 1978; 1978/242
    - A-U, 1978 (Reel 41, Frame 1083)
  - Puerto Rico, 1978; 1978/243
    - C-P, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1978; 1978/272
    - B-W, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 8)
  - South America, 1978; 1978/300
    - F-P, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 70)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/300.A
      - Panamerican Federation of Medical Schools, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 226)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/300.D
      - A-C, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 311)
  - Argentina, 1978; 1978/301
    - B-I, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 392)
  - Bolivia, 1978; 1978/303
    - Miranda P., Carlos, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 485)
  - Brazil, 1978; 1978/305
    - A-V, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 488)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/305.E
      - B-L, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 563)
  - Chile, 1978; 1978/309
    - C, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 575)
  - Colombia, 1978; 1978/311
    - B-U, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 830)
  - Costa Rica, 1978; 1978/313
    - I-U, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 907)
  - Guatemala, 1978; 1978/319
    - Gonzalez Arouz, Danilo, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 956)
  - Haiti, 1978; 1978/320
    - Sergile, Raoul, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 1002)
  - Honduras, 1978; 1978/321
    - A-R, 1978 (Reel 42, Frame 1009)
  - Mexico, 1978; 1978/323
    - A-V, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
  - Panama, 1978; 1978/327
    - I-P, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 261)
  - Peru, 1978; 1978/331
    - A-G, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 483)
  - El Salvador, 1978; 1978/333
    - de Sola, Francisco, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 503)
    - El Salvador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/339.D
      - Agriculture, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 506)
  - England, 1978; 1978/401
    - Imperial College of Science and Technology (Environmental Technology), 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 560)
    - A-M, 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 666)
    - National Institute for Medical Research (P-S), 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 901)
    - Open University (International Institute), 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 992)
    - Thomas, J.D., 1978 (Reel 43, Frame 1057)
    - N-W, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1)
  - Ireland, 1978; 1978/403
    - C-T, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 174)
  - Scotland, 1978; 1978/405
    - Ashton, D.P., 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 240)
  - Australia, 1978; 1978/410
    - A-L, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 242)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/410.A
      - University of Queensland, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 314)
  - New Zealand, 1978; 1978/418
    - J-R, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 318)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1978; 1978/420
    - C, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 324)
  - Canada, 1978; 1978/427
    - University of Alberta (Crossing Frontiers Conference), 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 641)
    - B-U, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 678)
  - Bermuda, 1978; 1978/430
    - Bermuda Biological Station, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 882)
  - Jamaica, 1978; 1978/437
    - Hunter, Lloyd B., 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 886)
  - India, 1978; 1978/464
    - A-T, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 888)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/464.A
      - All India Institute of Medical Sciences, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1051)
  - Pakistan, 1978; 1978/465
    - Mahmood, S. hamid, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1055)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1978; 1978/466
    - Cholera Research Laboratory, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1077)
  - Burma, 1978; 1978/468
    - DeDatta, Surajit K., 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1111)
  - Malaysia, 1978; 1978/473
    - B-R, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1135)
    - Malaysia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/473.D
      - Agriculture, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1159)
  - Nepal, 1978; 1978/474
    - Dhungel, Rajiv U., 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1169)
  - Africa, 1978; 1978/475
    - Council of Directors of Economic and Social Research Institutes in Africa, 1978 (Reel 44, Frame 1182)
  - Kenya, 1978; 1978/476
    - A-M, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - University of Nairobi (A-P), 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 183)
    - Kenya - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/476.D
      - Agriculture, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 289)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/476.E
      - M-N, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 297)
  - East Africa Region, 1978; 1978/477
    - Administration, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 347)
  - Rhodesia, 1978; 1978/483
    - Shiff, Clive J., 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 350)
  - South Africa Region, 1978; 1978/487
    - P-Y, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 356)
    - South Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/487.D
      - Agriculture, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 366)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1978; 1978/489
    - M-U, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 370)
    - Cape of Good Hope - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/489.A
      - University of Witwatersrand (Medical School), 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 379)
  - Uganda, 1978; 1978/492
    - A-M, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 381)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/492.E
      - Kivunja, Charles D., 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 389)
  - Sudan, 1978; 1978/494
    - D-U, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 392)
    - Sudan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/494.D
      - Agriculture, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 450)
  - West Africa, 1978; 1978/495
    - K-S, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 453)
  - Ghana, 1978; 1978/496
    - University of Ghana (Twum-Barima, K.), 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 467)
  - Nigeria, 1978; 1978/497
    - A-W, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 469)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/497.A
      - Ahmadu Bello University (E-M), 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 556)
  - France, 1978; 1978/500
    - Institute of Life, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 569)
    - C-S, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 894)
  - Senegal, 1978; 1978/531
    - Diouf, Jacques, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 1000)
  - China, 1978; 1978/601
    - E-P, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 1009)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/601.D
      - Study Teams, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 1013)
  - Taiwan, 1978; 1978/605
    - A-T, 1978 (Reel 45, Frame 1015)
  - Japan, 1978; 1978/609
    - N-U, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
  - Korea, 1978; 1978/613
    - K-M, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 8)
  - Thailand, 1978; 1978/617
    - C-S, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 38)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/617.E
      - S, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 134)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1978; 1978/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics), 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 150)
  - Holland, 1978; 1978/650
    - I-V, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 269)
  - Indonesia, 1978; 1978/652
    - G-T, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 288)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/652.E
      - Mochtar, Mas'oed, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 328)
  - Ethiopia, 1978; 1978/701
    - B-M, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 330)
    - Ethiopia - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/701.E
      - Molla, Aberra, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 340)
  - Belgium, 1978; 1978/707
    - L-P, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 360)
  - Belgian Congo, 19781978; 1978/709
    - I-N, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 384)
    - Belgian Congo - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/709.E
      - Sekimonyo, Wa Magango, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 407)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1978; 1978/712
    - University of Prague (Rysavy, D.B.), 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 410)
  - Germany, 1978; 1978/717
    - G-W, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 432)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/717.A
      - Heidelberg Institute of Tropical Medicine and Public Health, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 652)
  - Tanganyika, 1978; 1978/723
    - M-U, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 660)
    - Tanganyika - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/723.E
      - M, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 683)
  - Cameroon, 1978; 1978/735
    - University of Yaounde (Jalloh, Abdul-Aziz), 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 697)
  - Greece, 1978; 1978/749
    - American School of Classical Studies, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 699)
  - Italy, 1978; 1978/751
    - M-S, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 707)
  - Liberia, 1978; 1978/759
    - DeShield, McKinley A., Jr., 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 721)
  - Iran, 1978; 1978/771
    - Shahbanou Farah Foundation, 1978 (Reel 46, Frame 723)
  - Portugal, 1978/773
    - Portugal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1978; 1978/773.D
      - Agriculture, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 726)
  - Poland, 1978; 1978/789
    - M-W, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 850)
  - Sweden, 1978; 1978/800
    - K-S, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 888)
  - Switzerland, 1978; 1978/803
    - Nyffeler, J.P., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 960)
  - Turkey, 1978; 1978/805
    - M-R, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 964)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/805.E
      - A-Y, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 993)
  - Egypt, 1978; 1978/812
    - A-R, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 1118)
  - Jordan, 1978; 1978/816
    - Shoman Foundation, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 1)
  - Kuwait, 1978; 1978/822
    - Kuwait Fund for Arab Economic Development, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 11)
  - Israel, 1978; 1978/825
    - Hebrew University (C-M), 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 14)
    - University of Haifa (Wild Wheats), 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 196)
    - C-Y, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 308)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1978; 1978/825.A
      - Ben Gurion University, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 318)
  - Program and Policy, 1978/900
    - Program and Policy - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/900.E
      - Abrams, Natalie, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 321)
      - Ashton, Jean Willoughby, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 336)
      - Atherton, Margaret Louise, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 350)
      - Brown, Alison Pogrebin, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 359)
      - Callahan, Sidney DeS., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 410)
      - Cobb, Nina Kressner, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 414)
      - Cruise, Bryant B., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 448)
      - Jacoway, Elizabeth, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 506)
      - Kadish, Emily P., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 532)
      - Landesman, Joanne, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 547)
      - Lovell, Margaretta Markle, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 550)
      - Murphy, William Michael, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 577)
      - Ost, David E., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 610)
      - Siefert, Susan E., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 619)
      - C-V, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 659)
  - Members and Meetings, 1978; 1978/903
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M., 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 670)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 4th, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 918)
    - Taylor, Billy, 1978 (Reel 47, Frame 928)
    - C-W, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
  - Humanities, 1978; 1978/911
    - Segur, Nancy, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 253)
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/911.E
      - A-F, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 256)
      - Langer, Elinor, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 525)
      - Langer, Elinor (Supplementary Material), 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 598)
      - G-O, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 608)
      - P-W, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 856)
  - Environmental Affairs, 1978/927
    - Environmental Affairs - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/927.E
      - B-P, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 1077)
  - Geographic Medicine, 1978/928
    - Geographic Medicine - Fellowships, 1978; 1978/928.E
      - G-S, 1978 (Reel 48, Frame 1104)
- General Correspondence, 1979
  - International, 1979/100
    - Almy, Susan W., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Anderson, Bernard E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 3)
    - Anderson, R. Glenn, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 15)
    - Antoine, Pierre, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 25)
    - Arbab, Farzam, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 33)
    - Benson, Peter, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 95)
    - Biggs, Tyler S., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 99)
    - Black, Joseph E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 103)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 106)
    - Bronte, D. Lydia, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 160)
    - Bruer, John Thomas, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 183)
    - Buhr, Kenneth L., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 196)
    - Cahn, Steven M., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 219)
    - Christie, John D., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 221)
    - Clark, Carol A., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 226)
    - Colton, Joel, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 229)
    - Court, David, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 560)
    - Crowder, Loy V., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 563)
    - Dapice, David O., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 565)
    - Davidson, Ralph K., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 568)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 570)
    - Evans, John R., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 584)
    - Finfrock, Dwight C., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 588)
    - Gasbarre, Louis C., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 594)
    - Goffman, William, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 620)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 631)
    - Hildebrand, Peter E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 644)
    - Hopkins, Kevin D., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 740)
    - House, Leland R., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 874)
    - Jackson, Ben R., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 884)
    - Jennings, Peter R., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 905)
    - Johnson, Elmer C., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 937)
    - Johnston, James E., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 940)
    - Jordan, Peter, 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 957)
    - Kegler, Ella F., 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 963)
    - Knowles, John H. (China Diary), 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 965)
    - Knowles, John H. (Daedalus), 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 986)
    - Knowles, John H. (Memorial), 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 990)
    - Knowles, John H. (January-February), 1979 (Reel 1, Frame 1016)
    - Knowles, John H. (March), 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Knowles, John H. (April), 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 240)
    - Knowles, John H. (May-December), 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 351)
    - Kritz, Mary M., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 420)
    - Laird, Reggie J., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 426)
    - Lathem, Willoughby, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 530)
    - Lipkin, Mack, Jr., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 552)
    - Long, E. Croft, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 561)
    - Mann, Charles K., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 564)
    - Matteson, Patricia C., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 681)
    - Mauldin, W. Parker, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 817)
    - McDowell, Robert E., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 824)
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 832)
    - Mencher, Joan P., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 845)
    - Mock, Christopher Alden, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 852)
    - Moock, Joyce L., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 897)
    - Moomaw, James C., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 924)
    - Morris, Oliver Frank, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 928)
    - Nichols, Fred E., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 934)
    - Nyberg, Albert J., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 955)
    - Osby, William J., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 960)
    - Oshima, Harry T., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 962)
    - Osler, Robert D., 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 1105)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 1108)
    - Paulson, Jo Ann, 1979 (Reel 2, Frame 1111)
    - Pino, John A., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Plank, Stephen J., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 157)
    - Posner, Johsua L., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 159)
    - Pritchard, William Roy, 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 186)
    - Pryor, C. Anthony, 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 192)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 194)
    - Raun, Ned S., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 537)
    - Renfro, Bobby L., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 556)
    - Richardson, Ralph W., Jr., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 599)
    - Roberts, Lewis M., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 611)
    - Rohde, Jon E., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 621)
    - Romney, Henry, 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 735)
    - Scott, Virgil C., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 744)
    - Segal, Sheldon J., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 746)
    - Smeltzer, Dale G., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 760)
    - Snodgrass, Milton M., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 771)
    - Southern, Joseph W., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 776)
    - Spain, James M., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 803)
    - Stakman, Elvin C., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 839)
    - Starnes, Ordway, 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 861)
    - Stifel, Laurence D., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 889)
    - Tillman, Allen D., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 898)
    - Toenniessen, Gary H., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 973)
    - Velazquez Palau, Gabriel, 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 1005)
    - Walsh, Julia A., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 1011)
    - Warren, Kenneth S., 1979 (Reel 3, Frame 1013)
    - Waugh, Robert K., 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 198)
    - White, Kerr L., 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 258)
    - Willrich, Mason, 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 295)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling, 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 313)
    - Young, William R., 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 705)
    - A-Y, 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 745)
  - Requests for Information, 1979/102
    - K, 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 871)
  - International Organizations, 1979/103
    - International (A-L), 1979 (Reel 4, Frame 891)
    - International (O-V), 1979 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (C-T), 1979 (Reel 5, Frame 227)
    - United Nations (F), 1979 (Reel 5, Frame 920)
    - United Nations (I-T), 1979 (Reel 5, Frame 1045)
    - United Nations Center for Regional Development, 1979 (Reel 5, Frame 1067)
    - United Nations Development Programme (B-M), 1979 (Reel 5, Frame 1079)
    - United Nations Educational Scientific and Cultural Organization (Physical Education and Sport), 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - United Nations Fund for Population Activities, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 30)
    - United Nations University, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 33)
    - United Nations of Yoga, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 63)
    - A-D, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 112)
    - I-L, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 235)
    - W, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 353)
    - International Organizations - Schistosomiasis, 1979/103.W
      - United Nations, World Health Organization (Water Contact Studies), 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 406)
  - Agricultural Institute Development, 1979/104
    - Hess, David W., 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 409)
    - Monke, Eric Arthur, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 615)
    - B-M, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 690)
    - N-T, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 951)
  - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT), 1979/105
    - Economics, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 1170)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1979/120
    - African-US Artists Exchange, 1979 (Reel 6, Frame 1181)
    - Badash, Lawerence, 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Creger, William P., 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 68)
    - Kelman, Herbert C., 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 92)
    - Luard, David Evan Trant, 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 140)
    - Tolkki-Nikkonen, Mirja, 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 186)
    - B-W, 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 230)
  - Rockefeller/Ford Program for Population Policy Research, Declinations, 1979/150
    - Bhattacharyya, Amit K., 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 388)
  - Conflict in International Relations, Declinations, 1979/155
    - Koyate, Amadou G., 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 575)
  - United States, 1979/200
    - Aa-Af, 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 582)
    - Ag-Al, 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 676)
    - American Institutes for Research (Storytelling in America), 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 848)
    - American (A-I), 1979 (Reel 7, Frame 925)
    - American Land Forum, Inc., 1979 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - American National Red Cross, 1979 (Reel 8, Frame 120)
    - American Philosophical Association (Blacks in Philosophy), 1979 (Reel 8, Frame 322)
    - American (L-U), 1979 (Reel 8, Frame 494)
    - Am-Ar, 1979 (Reel 8, Frame 954)
    - Association of American Colleges (Status and Education of Women), 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Association (A-E), 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 70)
    - As-Au, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 93)
    - Baker, George E., Jr., 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 316)
    - Ball, Irene, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 333)
    - Bard College, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 388)
    - Berman, Edward H., 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 404)
    - Ba-Be, 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 517)
    - Bicentennial Council of the Thirteen Original States Fund, Inc., 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 844)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (of Chicago), 1979 (Reel 9, Frame 1020)
    - Blue Cross (of Western New York), 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Bi-Bl, 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 4)
    - Boston University (L-M), 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 124)
    - Bo, 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 175)
    - Bruce, John Allen, 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 478)
    - Br-Bu, 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 530)
    - California Council (of the Humanities in Public Policy), 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 655)
    - California State University, Long Beach (Video), 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 816)
    - Capture, George P. Horse, 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 920)
    - Carnegie Corporation (Foundation and Research Libraries Project), 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 959)
    - Case Western Reserve University (C-V), 1979 (Reel 10, Frame 989)
    - Ca, 1979 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Center (A-S), 1979 (Reel 11, Frame 393)
    - Central American Institute of Business Administration (Cruz, Ernesto), 1979 (Reel 11, Frame 822)
    - Chapple, Eliot D., 1979 (Reel 11, Frame 877)
    - Chapple, Eliot D. (Supplementary Material), 1979 (Reel 11, Frame 909)
    - Cheshire Home, 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Clapper, David L., 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 21)
    - Clark Foundation (C-S), 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 201)
    - Ce-Cl, 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 225)
    - Colorado State University (H-R), 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 454)
    - Columbia University (I-Z), 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 469)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 500)
    - Community Renewal Society (Community Job Assistance), 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 516)
    - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 776)
    - Cornell University (A-S), 1979 (Reel 12, Frame 968)
    - Council on Foundations, Inc. (Resumes), 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Council on Learning, 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 22)
    - Council (F-L), 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 124)
    - Council for Opportunity in Graduate Management Education, 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 150)
    - Co, 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 678)
    - Cr-Cu, 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 967)
    - DeBakey, Lois, 1979 (Reel 13, Frame 1059)
    - Da-Di, 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Duhl, Leonard J., 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 172)
    - Duhl, Leonard J. (Supplementary Material), 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 201)
    - Duke University (L-W), 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 536)
    - Do-Du, 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 685)
    - East-West Resource Systems Institute, 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 796)
    - Ea-Ei, 1979 (Reel 14, Frame 973)
    - Elderworks, 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Etheredge, Lloyd S., 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 101)
    - El-Ex, 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 419)
    - Fa-Fe, 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 615)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library, 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 644)
    - Ford Foundation (Libraries), 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 707)
    - Ford Foundation (A-S), 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 840)
    - Foundations, Greater New York Association of, 1979 (Reel 15, Frame 924)
    - Fi-Fo, 1979 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Fr-Fu, 1979 (Reel 16, Frame 442)
    - Gates Foundation (Health Maintenance Project), 1979 (Reel 16, Frame 639)
    - Gates Foundation, Health Maintenance Project (Supplementary Material), 1979 (Reel 16, Frame 869)
    - Ga-Gi, 1979 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Go-Gu, 1979 (Reel 17, Frame 201)
    - Hanan, Nina, 1979 (Reel 17, Frame 525)
    - Harvard University (Center for Middle Eastern Studies), 1979 (Reel 17, Frame 730)
    - Harvard University (C-W), 1979 (Reel 17, Frame 794)
    - H-Ha, 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Hein, Hilde Stern, 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 320)
    - Humphreys, George H., 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 404)
    - He-Hy, 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 422)
    - Indiana University (Poynter Center), 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 637)
    - Institute for Advanced Research in Asian Science and Medicine, 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 668)
    - Institute for Advanced Study (Einstein Centennial Symposium), 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 680)
    - Institute of International Education, 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 735)